acehardware.com 2012-10-11

# None

**Our Privacy Policy**

Ace Hardware Corporation ("Ace Hardware" or "we" or "us") recognizes that you care how information about you is collected and used. We have created this Privacy Policy to inform you of our information collection, use and sharing practices for this Web site, acehardware.com. 

Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy apply only to information gathered through this Web site and, where applicable, through our Customer Service Department in connection with this Web site, and do not necessarily reflect our practices with respect to information gathered through other Web sites that we operate or through other off-line means. 

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact our Customer Service Department by email at [customersupport@acehardware.com](mailto:customersupport@acehardware.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Questions). 

**_What Information About Me Is Collected?_**

**Information You Voluntarily Provide**

We collect and store information that you enter into this Web site or that you provide to our Customer Service Department in connection with this Web site. For example, information will be collected when you open or manage an account or an Ace Rewards membership account, when you place an order, when you sign up to receive emails, newsletters or other promotional communications, when you enter a contest or sweepstakes, when you contact us with online inquiries and/or when you otherwise voluntarily submit or provide information to us. The information we collect that you provide to us may include, but is not limited to: names, billing addresses, shipping addresses, email addresses, telephone numbers, Ace Rewards membership ID numbers, credit card numbers and expiration dates, account and log-in IDs, passwords, information regarding orders, demographic information and information regarding interests and preferences. This information is used to complete transactions and provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested, and for administrative and analytical purposes. For example, the information is used to process and ship orders, to send order and shipping confirmations, to manage billing and payment processes, to operate the Ace Rewards program, to provide emails, newsletters and other communications you have requested, to conduct audits, to manage our information and financial systems and to provide customer service. This information also may be used to contact you about sales, product recommendations, special offers and new site features from Ace Hardware and other selected vendors, unless you have opted not to receive promotional communications in connection with this Web site. When you opt not to receive emails, newsletters or other promotional information, we collect and store certain information, such as your email address, in order to comply with your preferences regarding such materials. 

**Information We Automatically Collect**

Like many Web sites, we use technologies to collect and store certain other information automatically whenever you interact with this Web site. For example, we collect your IP address, browser information and reference site domain name every time you visit this Web site. We also collect information regarding customer traffic patterns and site usage. This information is used to analyze and improve this Web site and to provide our customers with a fulfilling shopping experience. 

We may also use web beacons (also known as action tags, pixels, or transparent GIF files) to help manage online advertising. These web beacons are provided by our ad management partner(s) and enable our ad management partner(s) to recognize a unique cookie, which are files created by a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive by your Web browser. The cookie was placed by us or by another advertiser who works with our ad management partner(s). Web beacons allow us to learn which advertisements bring users to our Web site. They also allow us and our ad management partner(s) to collect information about your online activities so we can manage advertising effectiveness and provide you with online advertisements, including advertisements on other Web sites, more likely to be of interest to you. With web beacon technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. **For more information about online behavioral advertising and your choice to opt-out of receiving targeted online advertisements from members of the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA), please visit the DAA website by[clicking here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).**

Also, like many Web sites, we use cookies to help us to identify account holders and Ace Rewards members and to optimize their log-in, account management and shopping experience. Cookies also allow us to hold selections in a shopping cart when a user leaves this Web site without checking out. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. We recommend that you leave cookies "turned on" so that we can offer you a better experience on this Web site. 

**Mobile**

If you use our mobile Web site (m.acehardware.com), we may also collect information about your location. This information will be used to provide you with location-based services you request, such as store locations and local advertising. You may either provide this information to us or authorize us to obtain it from your wireless device. We do not retain information regarding your location, but your wireless device's operating system may store your authorization to provide us with information regarding your location. The length of time your authorization is stored will vary depending on your wireless device. While your authorization is stored, if you access or request location-based services on our mobile Web site, your mobile device will provide us with your location without additional authorization from you. If you would like to disable location services or change or revoke authorization by adjusting your mobile device's browser settings, please consult your mobile device's user guide. In addition, if you use our mobile Web site, we will automatically collect information regarding your wireless device, such as the type of device and its operating system. This information is used to analyze and optimize our mobile Web site. 

**Other Information**

We also may collect and store information about you that we receive from other sources, such as the U.S Postal Service National Change of Address (NCOA) service and providers of consumer data, to enable us to update and correct the information contained in our database and to provide product recommendations and special offers that we think will interest you. 

**_Is Information Collected From Children?_**

We do not sell any items ordered through this Web site directly to anyone who we know to be under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you should not use this Web site to submit orders or purchase any items. In addition, we do not collect online any personal information from anyone who we know to be under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you should use this Web site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian and should not submit any personal information of any kind to us. 

**_With Whom Do You Share Information?_**

We do not share with others any personal information that you provide to us through this Web site or through our Customer Service Department, except with your consent or as described in this Privacy Policy. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, personal information is information that you provide to us that personally identifies you, such as your full name, address, email address, phone number and credit card information. 

We engage third parties to perform services in connection with the operation of our business. Examples of these services include, but are not limited to, operation of our Web site(s), management of customer accounts and Ace Rewards accounts, payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, order fulfillment and shipping, gift card processing and management, marketing and promotional activities, Web site evaluation, data analysis and, where applicable, data cleansing. We may provide personal information to these third parties, but we authorize them to use this information only in connection with the services they perform on our behalf. We may permit such third parties to disclose personal information to subcontractors, but only if the third party limits the subcontractor?s use of such information to services performed on our behalf. 

If you are or become an Ace Rewards member, we may share personal information regarding you with the Ace Hardware retailer(s) in your area in order to facilitate your membership in the Ace Rewards program. 

We also may offer you the opportunity to purchase products and services provided by or in conjunction with third parties. If you purchase any of these products or services, we will provide your personal information to the third parties that provide the products and services that you request, but we authorize these third parties to use this information only in connection with the products and services they provide. We may also provide information, including personal information, about you to certain business partners, but only if you participate in programs offered by such business partners. 

We, or those with whom we have shared information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, may release personal information if we believe in good faith that: the law or legal process requires it; we have received a valid administrative request from a law enforcement agency; or such release is necessary or advisable to protect the rights, property or safety of Ace Hardware, or any of our respective affiliates, business partners, customers or others. We may also disclose personal information to assist us in the collection of amounts owed by you to us or to one of our business partners with whom you have authorized us to transact business on your behalf. 

We may share non-personal information with our marketing partners, advertisers and others from time to time. Examples of such non-personal information include the number of users who visited this Web site during a specific time period or purchased a specific product through this Web site. This information is shared in an aggregated form. 

We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you, including personal information, in connection with the sale or transfer of all or a portion of the business or assets of Ace Hardware to a third party. 

**_What Steps Are Taken To Keep Personal Information Secure?_**

We use various security measures, including Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology, to protect personal information that we collect. If you place an order through this Web site, you will be asked to set up an account and provide an email address and password. You must provide an appropriate email address and password in order to access account information. In order to help protect your personal information further, you should not provide your password to others. If you wish to cancel a password, or if you become aware of any loss, theft or unauthorized use of a password, please contact our Customer Service Department by email at [customersupport@acehardware.com](mailto:customersupport@acehardware.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Questions) or by phone at 1-866-290-5334. 

**_How Can I Access, Correct and Update Personal Information?_**

You can access, correct and update certain personal information that you have provided to us by clicking on "Manage Your Account" within the My Account area of this Web site. If you are an Ace Rewards member, you can update your Ace Rewards profile in the Ace Rewards area of this Web site. 

**_Can I Indicate Whether or Not I Want To Receive Promotional Communications?_**

There are several ways in which you can tell us whether or not you want to receive promotional communications from us. When you set up an account, or click on "Manage Your Account" within the My Account area, or place an order, you will have an opportunity to make or change your selections in this regard. You also will have an opportunity to change these selections by clicking on an "unsubscribe" hyperlink contained in promotional emails we send you. 

**_What Happens When I Link To or From Another Web Site?_**

This Web site may contain links to other Web sites operated by Ace Hardware and/or Web sites operated by third parties. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to information gathered through these other Web sites, including Web sites operated by Ace dealers. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave this Web site and to read the privacy policies of each and every Web site that you visit. 

If you have accessed this Web site through a link from certain of our advertising or marketing partners, this Web site may include a frame of the applicable advertising or marketing partner. Nevertheless, the information you provide to us through these framed Web pages is collected by us, and our use of this information is governed by this Privacy Policy. 

**_What About Contests and Sweepstakes?_**

When we run a contest or sweepstakes on this Web site, it will be accompanied by a set of rules. If our use of your personal information gathered in connection with the contest or sweepstakes entry process is different from the terms of this Privacy Policy, the rules for such contest/sweepstakes will specify how that information will be used. 

**_How Will I Be Informed About Changes Regarding This Privacy Policy?_**

Our Web site will continue to evolve to bring you new features and services and to implement technological advances. As a result, we may change this Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice. Revised versions of this Privacy Policy will be posted on this Web site, together with an updated effective date. In some cases, we may also send an email notifying users of the changes. You should check this Web site periodically to see if any recent changes to this Privacy Policy have occurred. By continuing to use this Web site after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified 

**_Effective Date_**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of **May 17th, 2012**.
